<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="account_list_page_first_account_button_done">[Åðð åççöûñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_list_page_first_account_message_detail">[Ŵĥéñ ýöû\'ŕé åšķéð ƒöŕ å véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé, ĝéţ îţ ĥéŕé. Ţĥé çöðé çĥåñĝéš ƒŕéqûéñţļý, šö ñö ñééð ţö mémöŕîžé îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="account_list_page_first_account_message_header">[Åççöûñţ åððéð one two]</string>
    <string name="accounts_reorder_failed">[Fåîļéð ţö ŕéöŕðéŕ åççöûñţš. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="add_account_label">[Åðð åççöûñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="advance_pending_import">[Öñ ţĥé öţĥéŕ ðévîçé, ĝö ţö QŔ çöðé ᐅ%1$dᐊ öƒ ᐅ%2$dᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="app_name">[Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="app_name_short">[Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_account_added">[Åððéð åççöûñţ \"ᐅ%sᐊ\" one two three four]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_exported_butterbar_text">[Åççöûñţš ŵéŕé ŕéçéñţļý éxþöŕţéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_exported_notification_text">[Ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ åççöûñţš ŵéŕé ŕéçéñţļý éxþöŕţéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_exported_notification_title">[Åççöûñţš éxþöŕţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_imported_butterbar_text">[Åççöûñţš ŵéŕé ŕéçéñţļý îmþöŕţéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_imported_notification_text">[Ýöû ŕéçéñţļý îmþöŕţéð šömé åççöûñţš îñţö Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_accounts_imported_notification_title">[Åççöûñţš îmþöŕţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_button">[Ŕéçéñţ åçţîvîţý one two]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_no_recent_events">[Ñö ŕéçéñţ évéñţš¡ one two three]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_page_description">[Åçţîöñš ýöû ĥåvé ŕéçéñţļý ţåķéñ ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ öñ ţĥîš ðévîçéññÑöţîçé åñýţĥîñĝ šûšþîçîöûš¿ ᐅᐊ Ŕéšéţ 2-Šţéþ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ ᐅᐊ öñ ţĥîš Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ åñð åñý öţĥéŕ åççöûñţš ýöû ûšé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone]</string>
    <string name="audit_log_page_title">[Ŕéçéñţ åçţîvîţý one two]</string>
    <string name="barcode_instruction_text">[Þļåçé QŔ çöðé ŵîţĥîñ ŕéð ļîñéš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="button_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="button_import_qr_code">[Šçåñ QŔ çöðé one two]</string>
    <string name="button_next">[Ñéxţ one]</string>
    <string name="button_previous">[Þŕévîöûš one]</string>
    <string name="camera_not_found_on_device_detail">[Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ ñééðš å çåméŕå ţö šçåñ QŔ çöðéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="camera_not_found_on_device_title">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé ðöéšñ\'ţ ĥåvé å çåméŕå one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="check_code">[Ţö çĥéçķ ţĥåţ ýöû ĥåvé ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ ķéý våļûé ƒöŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ véŕîƒý ţĥåţ ţĥé våļûé ĥéŕé måţçĥéš ţĥé îñţéĝŕîţý çĥéçķ våļûé þŕövîðéð бý ţĥé šéŕvéŕ:&lt;br/&gt; one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="check_code_menu_item">[Çĥéçķ ķéý våļûé one two]</string>
    <string name="check_code_title">[Îñţéĝŕîţý çĥéçķ våļûé one two three]</string>
    <string name="clipboard_label">[ÖŢÞ Çöðé one]</string>
    <string name="close">[Çļöšé one]</string>
    <string name="context_menu_remove_account">[Ŕémövé one]</string>
    <string name="copied_to_clipboard_toast">[Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé çöþîéð ţö çļîþбöåŕð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="copy_to_clipboard">[Çöþý ţö çļîþбöåŕð one two three]</string>
    <string name="counter_based_otp_type">[Çöûñţéŕ бåšéð one two]</string>
    <string name="counter_pin">[Ĝéţ çöðé one]</string>
    <string name="decoding_exception">[Ðéçöðîñĝ éxçéþţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="empty_pin">[_ _ _ _ _ _ one two three]</string>
    <string name="enroll2sv_choose_account_page_description">[Ûšé ţĥé QŔ çöðé öŕ šéţûþ ķéý îñ ýöûŕ 2FÅ šéţţîñĝš (бý Ĝööĝļé öŕ ţĥîŕð-þåŕţý šéŕvîçé). Îƒ ýöû\'ŕé ĥåvîñĝ ţŕöûбļé, ĝö ţö ĝ.çö/2šv one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
    <string name="enroll2sv_choose_account_page_enter_key_label">[Éñţéŕ å šéţûþ ķéý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="enroll2sv_choose_account_page_import_accounts_label">[Îmþöŕţ éxîšţîñĝ åççöûñţš¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="enroll2sv_choose_account_page_scan_barcode_label">[Šçåñ å QŔ çöðé one two three]</string>
    <string name="enroll2sv_choose_account_page_title">[Šéţûþ ýöûŕ ƒîŕšţ åççöûñţ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="enter_account_label">[Åççöûñţ ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="enter_account_name_missing">[Éñţéŕ å ñåmé ƒöŕ ţĥîš åççöûñţ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="enter_key_hint">[Ýöûŕ ķéý one]</string>
    <string name="enter_key_illegal_char">[Ķéý våļûé ĥåš îļļéĝåļ çĥåŕåçţéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="enter_key_page_add_button">[Åðð one]</string>
    <string name="enter_key_title">[Éñţéŕ åççöûñţ ðéţåîļš one two three]</string>
    <string name="enter_key_too_short">[Ķéý våļûé îš ţöö šĥöŕţ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="error_exists">[Šöŕŕý, ţĥåţ ñåmé îš åļŕéåðý îñ ûšé. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_device">[Çåññöţ åðð åççöûñţ. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ţĥé ŢéçĥŠţöþ ƒöŕ åššîšţåñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="error_outdated_migration">[Þļéåšé ûþðåţé ţĥîš åþþ îñ ţĥé Þļåý Šţöŕé îñ öŕðéŕ ţö šçåñ ţĥîš QŔ çöðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="error_qr">[Çåññöţ îñţéŕþŕéţ QŔ çöðé. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="error_title">[Éŕŕöŕ one]</string>
    <string name="error_uri">[Ķéý ñöţ ŕéçöĝñîžéð. one two three]</string>
    <string name="general_security_exception">[Ĝéñéŕåļ šéçûŕîţý éxçéþţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback_menu_item">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="how_it_works_menu_item">[Ĥöŵ îţ ŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_button_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_button_get_started">[Ĝéţ šţåŕţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_button_next">[Ñéxţ one]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_layout_1_description">[Ţö šéţûþ åñ åççöûñţ, ýöû\'ļļ šçåñ ţĥé QŔ çöðé îñ ýöûŕ 2-Šţéþ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ šéţţîñĝš ƒöŕ Ĝööĝļé öŕ åñý ţĥîŕð-þåŕţý šéŕvîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_layout_1_title">[Šîmþļé šéţûþ ûšîñĝ ýöûŕ çåméŕå one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_layout_2_description">[Ŵĥéñ ûšîñĝ 2-Šţéþ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ, ýöû\'ļļ éñţéŕ ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð åñð å çöðé ƒŕöm ţĥîš åþþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_layout_2_title">[Å ûñîqûé çöðé ûšéð ţö šîĝñ îñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="howitworks_page_title">[Ĥöŵ îţ ŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="keep_both_accounts">[Ķééþ бöţĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="main_preference_screen_title">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_barcode_page_title_multiple_codes">[Šçåñ QŔ çöðé ᐅ%1$dᐊ öƒ ᐅ%2$dᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_barcode_page_title_single_code">[Šçåñ ţĥîš QŔ çöðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_barcode_subtitle">[Ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ åþþ öñ ýöûŕ ñéŵ ðévîçé. Ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé åþþ, šçåñ ţĥîš QŔ çöðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_biometric_prompt_subtitle">[Ţö éxþöŕţ ýöûŕ åççöûñţš, ƒîŕšţ véŕîƒý îţ\'š ýöû one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_biometric_prompt_title">[Éxþöŕţ åççöûñţš one two]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_page_description">[Ţö éxþöŕţ, ŵé\'ļļ çŕéåţé å QŔ çöðé ţĥåţ šţöŕéš ţĥé åççöûñţš ýöû šéļéçţ бéļöŵ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_export_page_title">[Šéļéçţ åççöûñţš one two]</string>
    <string name="migration_import_page_instructions_step_1">[1. Ţåþ ţĥé övéŕƒļöŵ бûţţöñ åţ ţĥé ţöþ-ŕîĝĥţ öƒ ţĥé åþþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="migration_import_page_instructions_step_2">[2. Fîñð \"Ţŕåñšƒéŕ åççöûñţš\" ƒŕöm ţĥé méñû, ţĥéñ ƒöļļöŵ ţĥé îñšţŕûçţîöñš ţö çöñţîñûé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_import_page_subtitle">[Ýöû\'ļļ ñééð ţö šéļéçţ ţĥé åççöûñţš ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ţŕåñšƒéŕ ƒŕöm ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ åþþ öñ ýöûŕ öļð ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_import_page_title">[Ĝö ţö ýöûŕ öļð ðévîçé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="migration_menu_item">[Ţŕåñšƒéŕ åççöûñţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="migration_notification_channel_description">[Šéçûŕîţý åļéŕţš ŵĥéñ åççöûñţš ŵîţĥîñ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ åŕé ţŕåñšƒéŕŕéð бéţŵééñ ðévîçéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_notification_channel_name">[Åççöûñţ ţŕåñšƒéŕ åļéŕţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_introduction_description">[Ýöû çåñ ţŕåñšƒéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţš ţö å ñéŵ ðévîçé ţĥåţ ĥåš Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_introduction_export_description">[Çŕéåţé å QŔ çöðé ţö éxþöŕţ ýöûŕ åççöûñţš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_introduction_export_heading">[Éxþöŕţ åççöûñţš one two]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_introduction_import_description">[Šçåñ å QŔ çöðé ţö бŕîñĝ ñéŵ åççöûñţš îñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_introduction_import_heading">[Îmþöŕţ åççöûñţš one two]</string>
    <string name="migration_page_title">[Ţŕåñšƒéŕ åççöûñţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_camera_permission">[Ļéţ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ ûšé ýöûŕ ðévîçé\'š çåméŕå îƒ ýöû ŵåñţ ţö šçåñ QŔ çöðéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="not_update_button">[ÑÖ ŢĤÅÑĶŠ one two]</string>
    <string name="ok">[Öķåý one]</string>
    <string name="opensource_licenses_preference_title">[Öþéñ-šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="overwrite_alert_message">[Ýöû åļŕéåðý ĥåvé å Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ åççöûñţ çåļļéð \"ᐅ%sᐊ\" one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="overwrite_alert_title">[Åççöûñţ åļŕéåðý éxîšţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="overwrite_existing_account">[Ŕéþļåçé one]</string>
    <string name="permission_camera_rationale">[Ţö šçåñ QŔ çöðéš, ŵé ñééð ţĥé çåméŕå þéŕmîššîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="privacy_preference_title">[Þŕîvåçý þöļîçý one two]</string>
    <string name="remove_account_dialog_button_remove">[Ŕémövé åççöûñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="remove_account_dialog_message">[Ŕémövîñĝ ţĥîš åççöûñţ ŵîļļ &lt;b&gt;ŕémövé ýöûŕ åбîļîţý&lt;/b&gt; ţö ĝéñéŕåţé çöðéš, ĥöŵévéŕ, îţ ŵîļļ &lt;b&gt;ñöţ&lt;/b&gt; ţûŕñ öƒƒ 2-ƒåçţöŕ åûţĥéñţîçåţîöñ. Ţĥîš måý þŕévéñţ ýöû ƒŕöm šîĝñîñĝ îñţö ýöûŕ åççöûñţ. &lt;p&gt; Бéƒöŕé ŕémövîñĝ: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ţûŕñ öƒƒ 2-ƒåçţöŕ åûţĥéñţîçåţîöñ ƒöŕ ţĥîš åççöûñţ, öŕ&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Éñšûŕé ýöû ĥåvé åñ åļţéŕñåţé méçĥåñîšm ƒöŕ ĝéñéŕåţîñĝ çöðéš.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four]</string>
    <string name="remove_account_dialog_title">[Ŕémövé ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="rename">[Ŕéñåmé one]</string>
    <string name="save_key_message">[Šåvé ķéý ƒöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="secret_saved">[Šéçŕéţ šåvéð one two]</string>
    <string name="secret_saved_with_name">[Šéçŕéţ šåvéð åš \"ᐅ%sᐊ\" one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_item">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
    <string name="submit">[Šåvé one]</string>
    <string name="switch_ui_mode_dark">[Vîéŵ îñ ðåŕķ möðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="switch_ui_mode_light">[Vîéŵ îñ ļîĝĥţ möðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="tap_to_show">[Ţåþ ţö šĥöŵ çöðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="terms_preference_title">[Ţéŕmš öƒ šéŕvîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="time_based_otp_type">[Ţîmé бåšéð one two]</string>
    <string name="timesync_about_feature_preference_title">[Åбöûţ ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé one two three]</string>
    <string name="timesync_preference_screen_title">[Ţîmé çöŕŕéçţîöñ ƒöŕ çöðéš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_connectivity_error_dialog_details">[Ţĥéŕé ŵåš å þŕöбļém çöñţåçţîñĝ Ĝööĝļé\'š šéŕvéŕ. Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_connectivity_error_dialog_title">[Šýñç ñöŵ one]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_preference_title">[Šýñç ñöŵ one]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_progress_dialog_details">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö šéŕvéŕ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_progress_dialog_title">[Šýñç ñöŵ one]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_screen_title">[Šýñç ñöŵ one]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_time_already_correct_dialog_details">[Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ\'š îñţéŕñåļ çļöçķ ŵåš ñöţ åðĵûšţéð бéçåûšé îţ åþþéåŕš ţö åļŕéåðý бé îñ šýñç ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé šéŕvéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_time_already_correct_dialog_title">[Ţîmé åļŕéåðý çöŕŕéçţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_time_corrected_dialog_details">[Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ\'š îñţéŕñåļ çļöçķ ĥåš бééñ åðĵûšţéð ţö måţçĥ ţĥé ţîmé þŕövîðéð бý Ĝööĝļé šéŕvéŕš. ññŢĥé Ðåţé &amp; Ţîmé šéţţîñĝš öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé ĥåvé ñöţ бééñ çĥåñĝéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]</string>
    <string name="timesync_sync_now_time_corrected_dialog_title">[Ţîmé çöŕŕéçţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="type_prompt">[Ţýþé öƒ ķéý one two]</string>
    <string name="update_button">[ÛÞÐÅŢÉ one]</string>
    <string name="update_google_play_services_for_security_key">[Ûþðåţé &lt;b&gt;Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Šéŕvîçéš&lt;/b&gt; ţö ûšé Šéçûŕîţý Ķéý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="welcome_page_details">[Ĝéţ véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðéš ƒöŕ åļļ ýöûŕ åççöûñţš ûšîñĝ 2-Šţéþ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="welcome_page_headline">[Šţŕöñĝéŕ šéçûŕîţý ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Åûţĥéñţîçåţöŕ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
</resources>
